https://www.radial.com/legal/website-user-privacy-notice

Skip to main content
Website User Privacy Notice
Mobile Overlay
< Back to Legal
This privacy notice describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information.
Effective Date
This Notice was updated on December 18, 2019. Contents & Summary
Scope and Consent
This privacy
notice describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use, disclosure,
retention, and protection of your personal information. It applies to any
Radial Sites (defined below) where this notice appears in the footer,
regardless of how you access or use them, including mobile devices. You should
read it to learn how Radial will process and protect your data.
By
using this site or any related sites (collectively, “Sites”) where this Privacy
Notice is displayed or referenced, you expressly consent to the terms of this
Privacy Notice.
Learn more
Privacy Shield Certification
Radial
has certified that it adheres to the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Principles for all
onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the onward transfer
liability provisions.
Learn more
Collection
We
collect different types of information on the Sites in order to provide you
with the use of and access to our Sites, and to help us personalize and improve
your experience on the Sites. This includes information we collect
automatically (such as device ID, device type, geo-location information,
computer and connection information, statistics on page views, traffic to and
from the sites, referral URL, ad data, IP address, standard web log
information, and anonymous information collected through our use cookies and
web beacons) and information you give us (such as information you enter on our
Sites or you provide to us in context of using our Sites).
Learn more
Use and Retention
We use
the personal information we collect to: operate, improve and personalize our
Sites and services, to contact you about our services, and to customize our
advertising and marketing.
We retain your personal information only as long as it is necessary and relevant
for our operations.
Learn more
Choice
You
have a choice about how we use your personal information to communicate with
you, send you marketing information, and provide you with customized and relevant
advertising.
Learn more
Access
If you
have provided us with your personal information and wish to update, correct, or
delete it, you have the ability to contact us as indicated below. We will
respond to any access requests within a reasonable timeframe.
If your
personal information was provided to us by a Radial client and you wish to
update, correct or delete it, please contact that company directly.
Learn more
Disclosure
There
are times when we disclose your personal information to members of the Radial
corporate family or other third parties. We do not disclose your personal information
to unaffiliated third parties for their marketing and advertising purposes
without your explicit consent.
Learn more
Personal Information Rights for California and European Residents
Recent changes in laws have created specific rights for residents of California and European Union countries (including the United Kingdom should it exit the EU).
These rights are created by the California Consumer Privacy Act of 2018 (“CCPA”), the EU General Data Protection Regulation (“GDPR”) and other applicable data privacy laws.
A description of these rights and how to exercise these rights are described in the privacy notice located here.
Learn more
Security
We
store and process your personal information on our computers in the US and
elsewhere in the world, where we use reasonable measures in an attempt to
protect your information, such as using physical, technical, and administrative
security measures to reduce the risks of loss, misuse, unauthorized access,
disclosure, or alteration.
Learn more
Important Information
This
section describes some additional important information related to your use of
our Sites. Please review it for more details.
Learn more
Questions or Complaints
Questions
regarding this Privacy Notice should be directed to Radial by email to privacy@radial.com or
by regular mail to the attention of: Privacy Manager, Radial, 935 First Avenue,
King of Prussia, PA 19406.
Learn more
Scope Anchor
Scope and Consent
This
privacy notice describes your privacy rights regarding our collection, use,
disclosure, retention, and protection of your personal information. It also
describes your choices regarding use, access and correction of your personal
information. It applies to any Radial Site where this notice appears in the
footer, and to any Radial application, service, or tool where this notice is
referenced, regardless of how you access or use them, including mobile devices.
You should read it to learn how Radial will process and protect your data.
By using the Sites where this Privacy Notice is displayed or referenced, you
expressly consent to the terms of this Privacy Notice.
If all
or part of Radial is sold, merged, or otherwise transferred to another entity,
the information gathered by the transferred entity may be transferred as part
of that transaction.
Personal
Information
Throughout this Privacy Notice, we use the terms “personal information” or
“personal data” to describe any information relating to an identified or
identifiable natural person, such as full name, email address, mailing address,
IP address or other information used to identify a computer or browser, and business
contact information. We do not consider as personal data information that has
been made anonymous so that it can no longer be used, whether in combination
with other information or otherwise, to identify a specific person.
Changes
to This Notice
We may amend this Privacy Notice at any time by posting the amended terms on
this Site. Any such amendment shall take effect when such amendment is posted
on the Site (unless changes are material).  If we make any material
amendments, we will notify you by email (sent to the email address you
provided) or by means of a notice on this Site prior to the amendment taking
effect.
Privacy Shield Anchor
Privacy Shield Certification
Radial,
including members of the Radial corporate family, such as Radial South, L.P.,
participates in, and has certified its compliance with, the EU-U.S. Privacy
Shield Framework.  Radial is committed to subjecting all personal data
received from European Union (EU) member countries, in reliance on the Privacy
Shield Framework, to the Framework’s applicable Principles.  To learn more
about the Privacy Shield Framework, visit the U.S.
Department of Commerce’s Privacy Shield List.
Radial
is responsible for the processing of personal data it receives, under the
Privacy Shield Framework, and subsequently transfers to a third party acting as
an agent on its behalf.  Radial complies with the Privacy Shield
Principles for all onward transfers of personal data from the EU, including the
onward transfer liability provisions.
With
respect to personal data received or transferred
pursuant to the Privacy Shield Framework, Radial is subject to the regulatory
enforcement powers of the U.S. Federal Trade Commission.  In certain
situations, Radial may be required to disclose personal data in response to
lawful requests by public authorities, including to meet national security or
law enforcement requirements.
If you
have an unresolved privacy or data use concern that we have not addressed
satisfactorily, please contact our U.S.-based third party dispute resolution
provider (free of charge) at https://feedback-form.truste.com/watchdog/request.
Under certain conditions, more fully described on the Privacy Shield website, you may invoke binding arbitration when other dispute resolution procedures
have been exhausted.
Collection Anchor
Collection
Categories
of Individual Data Subjects
In general, Radial may obtain EU Personal Data in the United States about
several different types of individuals, including consumers, Clients (defined
below), suppliers and other business partners. Radial's practices with respect
to each of these types of individual data subjects are described below.
Consumers
Radial provides a wide variety of services and solutions to its business
clients (each, a "Client") that facilitate services for their
customers ("Consumers"). In these cases, personal data collected from
Consumers is owned by the applicable Client, and Radial processes this data on
the Client's behalf. There may be limited instances in which Radial owns and processes
personal data collected from Consumers on its own behalf, rather than on behalf
of a Client. In all instances, Radial will obtain access to EU Personal Data
about Consumers in the course of operating websites, processing payments,
fulfilling orders, implementing marketing campaigns and providing customer care
and other related services. Such data may include, name, billing address,
shipping address, email address, telephone number, credit card or other payment
information, and other information, depending on the particular Client, website
or other application at issue. In all instances, Radial will not share, sell,
rent, or trade with third parties for promotional purposes any personal data
processed by Radial, unless Radial is directed to do so by a Client who owns
such personal data.
Clients,
Suppliers and Other Business Partners
Radial may obtain various types of EU Personal Data about employees and agents
of its Clients, suppliers and other business partners. Such data may include
contact information (e.g. names, addresses, telephone and fax numbers, and
email addresses); user IDs and passwords; information collected through
Internet-based and ecommerce activities; and other transaction-related data.
Radial may use these types of EU Personal Data for business purposes, including
to establish and maintain Client, supplier and other business relationships; to
deliver or provide products or services; to provide access to Internet-based
applications; to perform accounting functions; and to conduct other activities as
necessary or appropriate in connection with the establishment, servicing and
development of the business relationship.
Why We
Collect Information
We (including all members of our corporate family) may collect and use the
information collected at our Sites to contract you and provide you with the
information your requested, and to help us design and deliver better services
to our clients. For example, we may use this data to monitor our Sites and to
collect aggregate data for marketing purposes and for other future uses, or to
determine the most appropriate information to send to those who request it.
You may
choose voluntarily to give us personally identifiable information, such as your
name, address, phone number, email address, or other information about
yourself.  In addition, we may collect information automatically as you
navigate our sites. This information may include (but may not be limited to): general
location data, IP address, browser type, Internet service provider (ISP),
referring/exit pages, the files viewed on our sites (e.g., HTML pages,
graphics, etc.), operating system, date/time stamp, clickstream data, device
data such as mobile identifiers, carrier network information, the mobile
website or mobile app used, and cookie or pixel tag data.
Certain
forms on our sites may also request contact and profile information, such as
user name, email address, website, phone number, or company information.
Completion of these forms is entirely voluntary but may be required in order to
request certain services from Radial. Resume submissions on our Sites are used
to screen candidates and contact them for interviews.
Radial
may also use our sites to periodically survey our clients for purposes of
improving the quality of our service and customer satisfaction. Client
participation is completely voluntary, and any information we collect from you
as part of our surveys will be treated with the same respect as any other
information gathered in accordance with this Notice.
How We
Collect ItAs explained above we collect information through surveys, forms
on our websites and in our daily interactions with our clients and vendors. Please
note that we only obtain personal information that can be used to contact you,
such as your name, address, phone number or email address, if it is supplied to
use voluntarily.
Also, our Sites use web beacons and other technologies to collect information
when you access our websites, and we may store that information in “cookies”.
If you
have chosen to receive marketing messages from us about our products and
services, we may use information from our log files, cookies, or web beacons to
help us make those communications more useful or interesting to you. We may
periodically track the open-rates and click behavior of our emails and other
messages and advertisements to help us identify which portions of our
advertisements are most popular and effective with our customers.
How We
Use Cookies and Other Technologies
When you access our sites, we and our affiliates, business partners and vendors
may place small data files on your computer or other device. We use these data
files, commonly known as “Cookies” to help us identify you as a site visitor or
Client, customize our content and enhance your site experience. These third
parties may also use a technology called “Tags” or “Web Beacons”. Similar in
function to Cookies, Web Beacons allow us to understand the movements of
visitors to our Sites. The tracking technologies on our Sites do not collect
personal information that can be used to contact you, such as your name,
address, phone number or email address. We use this information to analyze
trends, to administer our Sites, to track users' movements around the Sites,
and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.
However, please note that tracking technologies do collect identifiers that
could be considered personal information under certain regulations.
You
should note that although most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies,
you may be able to change your browser settings to cause your browser to refuse
first party or third-party cookies or to indicate when a third-party cookie is
being sent. However, disabling or limiting cookies may cause certain features
of this site to not function properly.  Check
your browser’s “Help” files or other similar resources to learn more about
handling cookies on your browser.Data
Supplementation
We may receive information about you from other sources, including publicly
available databases or third parties from whom we have purchased data, and
combine this data with information we already have about you.  This helps
us to update, expand and analyze our records, identify new customers, and
provide products and services that may be of interest to you. Examples of the
types of personal information that may be obtained from public sources or
purchased from third parties and combined with information we already have
about you may include address information about you from third party sources,
such as the U.S. Postal Service, to verify your address. This information is
used for payment processing, fraud prevention and fulfillment services.
Do Not
Track
California law requires us to state how we respond to Do Not Track (DNT)
signals. Because there is currently no industry or legal standard for
recognizing or honoring DNT, we do not currently respond to DNT signals. We
await the result of work by the privacy community and industry to determine
when such a response is appropriate and what form it should take.
Use Anchor
Use and Retention
Use
We use the information we gather to help us improve our services to offer the
best user experience possible, to communicate with our Clients, or for other
internal purposes and to generally operate the Sites. You agree that we may use
your personal information as follows:
To deliver information specific to your
interests
To create a profile detailing your service
preferences so that we can best serve you
To save you from having to re-enter your password each time you visit our site
To better analyze our site traffic patterns so that we can bolster our Web offering
To respond to your questions or to provide you with the information you have requested
Any non-personally
identifiable material, information, suggestions, ideas, concepts, know-how,
techniques, questions, comments, or other communication you transmit or post to
our Sites in any manner will be considered non-confidential and non-proprietary
"User Communications." Radial and each of our affiliates and/or their
designees may use any or all User Communications for any purpose whatsoever,
including, without limitation, reproduction, transmission, disclosure,
publication, broadcast, development, manufacturing and/or marketing in any
manner whatsoever for any or all commercial or non-commercial purposes.
Retention
We retain your personal
information only as long as it is necessary and relevant for our operations.
In addition, we retain
personal information from closed accounts to: comply with the law, prevent
fraud, collect any fees owed, resolve disputes, troubleshoot problems, assist
with any investigation, and take other actions permitted by law.
Choice Anchor
Choice
You
have a choice about how we use your personal information to communicate with
you, send you marketing information, and provide you with customized and
relevant advertising.
Advertising
We may partner with a third
party to manage our advertising on other sites. Our third party partner may use
cookies or similar technologies in order to provide you advertising based upon
your browsing activities and interests. If you wish to opt out of
interest-based advertising click here or if located in the
European Union, click here. Please note you will continue to receive generic ads. Marketing
We do not sell or rent your
personal information to third parties for their marketing purposes without your
explicit consent. We may combine your information with information we collect
from other companies and use it to improve and personalize our services or
content.
You may opt-out of the
marketing messages we send at any time by utilizing the unsubscribe information
provided in such message or by contacting us at privacy@radial.com.
If you choose to
unsubscribe from emails, please click unsubscribe in the applicable email
message. Rarely, we may need to contact you regarding non-promotional purposes.
You cannot opt out of these operational emails.
Access Anchor
Access to Information
Upon
request Radial will provide you with information about whether we hold, as
a data controller, any of your personal information. You may
access, correct, or request deletion of your personal information by emailing
us at privacy@radial.com.
We will respond to your request within a reasonable timeframe, and not exceeding
45 calendar days (if you are located in the EEA or you are subject to their
data protection regulations).
Radial
acknowledges that you have the right to access your personal information.
In most instances, Radial has no direct relationship with the individuals
whose personal data it processes. An individual who seeks access, or who seeks
to correct, amend, or delete inaccurate data should direct their query to
Radial’s Client (the data controller). If requested to remove data we will
respond within a reasonable timeframe and not exceeding 45 calendar days (if
you are located in the EEA or you are subject to their data protection
regulations). If you are a customer of one of our Clients and would no longer
like to be contacted by one of our Clients that uses our service, please
contact the Client directly. We may transfer personal information to companies
that help us provide our service. Transfers to subsequent third parties are
covered by the service agreements with our Clients or vendors, as applicable.
Disclosure Anchor
Disclosure
We and our affiliates may
collect and use the information collected at our Sites for the reasons stated
above (please see our Use Section) and provide that information to our business
partners and vendors to be used by them for such related purposes. We may also
disclose personal information to respond to legal requirements, enforce our
policies, respond to claims that user or Client content violates the rights of
others, or protect anyone's rights, property, or safety. Such information will
be disclosed in accordance with this Privacy Notice and applicable laws and
regulations. As stated above, we never disclose your personal information to
unaffiliated third parties for their marketing purposes without your explicit
consent.
We may also share your
personal information with:
Members of the Radial
corporate family to provide joint content and services (such as registration,
transactions, and customer support), to share contact information and basic
corporate information with sister companies for the purpose of marketing other
products and services that may be relevant to your business, to help detect and
prevent potentially illegal acts, violations of our policies, fraud and/or data
security breaches, and to guide decisions about products, services, and
communications.
Service providers under
contract who help with parts of our business operations such as marketing and
technology services. Our contracts dictate that these service providers only
use information in connection with the services they perform for us and not for
their own benefit;
personal information is necessary to prevent physical harm or financial loss,
to report suspected illegal activity or to investigate violations of our User
Agreements.
Companies that we plan to
merge with or be acquired by.
Any other third party with
your prior consent.
If you use a bulletin
board, chat room, blog, or other public forum function on our Sites, you should
be aware that any personal information you submit there may be read, collected,
or used by other users of these forums, and could be used to send you
unsolicited messages. We are not responsible for the personal information you
choose to submit in these forums.
Security Anchor
Security
We store and process your
personal information on our computers in the US and elsewhere in the world
where our facilities are located. We protect your information using reasonable
technical and administrative security measures in an effort to reduce the risks
of loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure and alteration. Some of the
safeguards we use are firewalls and data encryption, physical access controls
to our data centers, and information access authorization controls. Still, no system can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. If you have
questions about the security of your personal information, or if you have
reason to believe that the personal information that we hold about you is no
longer secure, please contact us immediately as described in this Privacy
Notice.
Important Info Anchor
Important Information
Children’s Privacy
The Radial Sites are
general audience websites and are not intended for children under the age of
13. We do not knowingly collect personal information via our Sites from users
in this age group. If we discover we have inadvertently gathered any personal
information from this age group, appropriate steps will be taken to delete it. Third Parties
This Privacy statement only
applies to information received or collected by Radial Sites or information
received and processed by Radial (and all members of its corporate family) from
its Clients or its Clients’ third-party vendors. Our Sites do not control the
privacy practices of third parties. Consumers who click on a link or
advertisement, visit a third-party site, or interact with third-party content
are subject to the privacy policies of those third parties, where applicable.
Questions Anchor
Questions or Complaints
Questions regarding this
Privacy Notice should be directed to Radial by email to privacy@radial.com or
by regular mail to the attention of:
